I'm struggling with this video because I
don't want to say the wrong thing like
Simone's gonna actually watch this and I
don't want I feel like my story's a bit
like telling a pregnant woman or
pregnant person same disastrous stories
about birth like it's like okay you're
on this side of it but since she's not
gonna watch it maybe someone else who's
going through this process well trigger
warning that it's not necessarily a good
outcome but it leads to a good outcome I
have always been someone who values
intellect and knowledge and so my vision
of being on this planet was to cram as
much information as I cut into my head
my whole life like just learn learn
learn learn and so that meant from
adolescence onward I was learning about
science and economics and health and
self-help psychology and politics and
history his language is not languages
but like learning that at least that's
always been a sticking point no matter
what but a language word vocabulary
knowing that I was deficient and then
trying to learn learn those pieces and
looking up words to know what their
definition is and memorizing the piece
like it was just like shove as much
information in and then when I was 25
and my third year of university I was
diagnosed with a brain tumor had it
removed my brain swelled after because I
they didn't keep me on steroids long
enough and my GP and roommate didn't
know the signs so I had some brain
damage from that I still finished my
years of university my year and a half
left of University and I went on with my
life
then I got radiation five years later
cuz it did grow back
it was growing back and that killed the
tumor but it also had an effect on my
neurological system I've been sensitive
to sound I was maybe always and light
and smell which I wasn't before I've had
just like an altered neuro system and
dealing with my body's response to
stress and every stressful event made it
worse and worse and figuring that out is
what cost me more so than the event that
that is my new normal that I can't
handle straw
it was not being listened to in the
medical community and still having to
advocate for myself that caused the most
issues and still causes the most issues
but having an altered brain for me has
been the biggest blessing because it's
like that's where I'm like the pregnant
alliance all the wrong story that this I
was supposed to have an alter brain I
was supposed to have this happen so that
I could stop cramming new information in
and work with what I would already had
because otherwise I'd just be out
cramming new information other people's
new information I wouldn't be
discovering what I'm put here to do
which is both to fix it all to help
other people be the pieces that have
been helped fix at all because we all
have pieces and we're not great other
people are and that's the like beauty of
humanity's diversity is that even though
and she already knows Simone already
knows had it like I stopped my brain at
a certain point to a certain degree so
I'm like people like you need to edit
your videos are my brain so my videos
and like you only know how you're gonna
how to edit videos you're running out
the following and you already know the
robots so even if your brain did what
mine did you'd still have that
information and be able to work with it
even if you weren't able to put in new
information and that sounds scary
especially if somebody's very
intellectual but like I said it's been
the biggest blessing and because now I'm
like oh I just had to like sit and remix
all of the information I already had
which luckily was a lot because I was
obsessed with putting in a lot of
information and my personal journey in
her journey because I had to stop
concentrating on intellect and so like
well how do I grow if I can't learn and
it was more about right there's this
whole other side of you you cut off this
emotional feeling inside that's also
important so digging into that more and
realizing the beauty there and be more
than ever authentic to the outside okay
explain to someone who has it with your
health struggles that when you've gone
through them there's a lot of blessing
there if
opening to it that my I had to mourn
what I lost and that led to a couple
years of depression because I still had
this version of me that was supposed to
be that I was supposed to be able to
learn more and like what can I do if I
can't work in lab if I can't do all the
things I thought I would be able to do
I can't work full-time I can't work for
anyone else it was like right because
you're not supposed to you're supposed
to work for yourself you're supposed to
work for Humanity you're supposed to
work from where you are and every time I
go in and get more messages for my
guides in the universe and meditation
it's not my personality is still
perfected it's not good enough it's not
like you need to invent video this is
shit business and it's it's but the
message from the guides is like no put
yourself out there like this this is
what you're supposed to do I get that no
one else is like no this is pretty
shitty but um for me because putting
myself out there as I am means the right
people I'm not going to go viral that's
fine I need to find the people someone
who's gonna add up the video if that's
the road we go someone who is gonna
manage the people because that's not my
strong point I'm like how does that an
email I'm just added 10 million emails
no no that's scary and yet that's what
we need we need 10,000 people than a
hundred thousand people than a million
people I'm not the person who's gonna be
able to do that I only have the message
and I struggle with communicating it
which is its own things I'm like write
the book do sin it's I can't sit down
and focus to be able to do that I can't
edit either video or words because it's
too much computation of light figure you
know which should be and shouldn't be
and that's too much for my brain but
other people that's easy for so there's
part of your life right but no one else
is gonna come on board and write out my
thoughts for me except yeah they
actually might someone that might
actually speak to them and so I'm just
doing what I can from my place in the
world from where my brain works and my
body works and it has been the biggest
blessing and all of this shit I would
not have found out on my own if I hadn't
gone through all this shit like it would
not have happened
because I would have just been crowned
me more information in my head I would
have just been listening to what society
says is valid instead of looking in or
of like no no Who am I who without my my
knowledge without people think people
don't think I'm smart if I don't think
I'm smart what does that mean and the
truth is people stop I'm smart if
anything I have to prove the other side
I'm like again I have a good vocabulary
but I don't because I can't find the
word and my brain doesn't follow the
path and it's like it's it's a struggle
but it's also I know that I have much
more capacity for learning than some
people do that never had had brain
damage have I never had this brain
altering damage that I wanted to get but
truth is radiation has outcomes
especially when they happen on your
brain some which are very short-term
nausea and things like I'm not supposed
to have the sensitivity to light sound
and smells almost 10 years on but I do
but other people don't like that's not
common at all and it kills tumors and if
there is side effects if there are
things that happen you will still find
joy in it you can still as long as
you're alive you can still find the
beauty and what you do have to offer and
like you said you already have the
franchise you already have the people
that like love you and care about you
and although you never have to be very
tumor girl if you take even just a tiny
bit of that like it's part of your
journey and part of your story and it
makes you more of a warrior and more
kick-ass and more sympathetic for other
people who are going through things like
that it just makes you a better human
being and also brings people that maybe
are drawn to your story through that to
see the rest of it because that's how I
found her is because I clicked on brain
tumor story not amazing horrible robot
builder and so this has gone way longer
than five minutes but in day two of my
new date